<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Spencer Woody</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Spencer Woody</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Making nice maps</title>
      <link>/post/2019/10/30/making-nice-maps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/10/30/making-nice-maps/</guid>
      <description>Structure of workflow Get ACS study via tidycensus, which gives sf spatial objects, each with data annotation Get geographic layers via rmapzen Convert geographic layes to sf objects using the sf package Use ggplot2 for vizualization.  Much of this workflow has been taken from a post by Dmitri Shkolnik.
library(sf) library(ggplot2) library(cowplot) theme_set(theme_half_open()) library(tidycensus) library(sf) library(dplyr) library(tigris) library(rmapzen) ## You need API keys (Census &amp;amp; mapzen) to use these packages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My PhD oral exam</title>
      <link>/post/2018/11/25/my-phd-oral-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/11/25/my-phd-oral-exam/</guid>
      <description>I recently gave to a talk which counted as my oral examination to officially enter candidacy. This talk mostly concerned work on post-selection inference that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed with my advisor James Scott, but it also briefly introduced some ongoing work concerning posterior summarization.
My committee members are:
 Professor James Scott (advisor) Professor Carlos Carvalho Professor Jared Murray Professor Cory Zigler  Slides from my talk are available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UQ Mini Workshop</title>
      <link>/post/2018/09/15/uq-mini-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/09/15/uq-mini-workshop/</guid>
      <description>This summer I was lucky enough to collaborate with Lauren Hund from Sandia National Laboratories on some work related to uncertainty quantification (UQ) and Bayesian model calibration. We worked together to extend ideas on power likelihood methods to a model calibration problem originally published earler this year in JRSS C. Novin Ghaffari, another PhD student at UT, also worked with Lauren, though Novin worked on a problem of combining subset posteriors and so his work did not intersect much with mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;m doing this summer</title>
      <link>/post/2018/05/29/what-im-doing-this-summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/05/29/what-im-doing-this-summer/</guid>
      <description>Work I&amp;rsquo;m doing  Collaborating with Sandia National Labs on Bayesian model calibration and uncertainty quantification under model misspecification Original research on post-selection inference, for application to sparse normal means problem and spatial hotspot detection  Conferences I am attending ACIC Atlantic Causal Inference Conference
May 21 - 23, 2018
Carnegie Melon University
Pittsburgh, PA
ISBA ISBA World Meeting 2018
June 24 - 29, 2018
University of Edinburgh
United Kingdom</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/papers/</guid>
      <description>Pre-prints and papers under review  Spencer Woody, Mauricio Garcia Tec, Maytal Dahan, Kelly Gaither, Spencer Fox, Lauren Ancel Meyers, and James G. Scott. “Projections for first-wave COVID-19 deaths across the US using social-distancing measures derived from mobile phones.” [medRxiv preprint].
 S. Woody, O.H.M Padilla and J.G. Scott. &amp;ldquo;Optimal post-selection inference for sparse signals: a nonparametric empirical-Bayes approach.&amp;rdquo; 2020. [arXiv preprint] [code].
 S. Woody, C.M. Carvalho and J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software/</guid>
      <description>saFAB Bayes-optimal frequentist confidence intervals for selected parameters. Companion R package to this paper by me and James G. Scott.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>2020-04-30
SDS 384 Causal Inference Methodology Final Project, University of Texas at Austin
Matching methods for categorical and continuous treatments
 2019-10-11
SDS Seminar, University of Texas at Austin
Model Interpretation through Posterior Summarization
 2019-05-22
ACIC 2019, McGill University, Montreal, Canada
Posterior Summarization for the Causal Linear Model (poster)
 2018-11-13
PhD oral examination, University of Texas at Austin
Bayes-optimal post-selection inference; posterior summarization
 2018-09-14
UQ Mini Workshop, University of Texas at Austin</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>